* Skip to main content

Search

Close

Open

* * About Us
        
        Arrow Right
        
* * News & Media
        
        Arrow Right
        
* * Sustainability
        
        Arrow Right
        
* * Doing Business with Us
        
        Arrow Right

* Search
    
    Close

Please don't fill out this field 

Search 

SearchSearch

Kodak Privacy Notice
====================

Updated December 2022

Our Commitment to Privacy
-------------------------

At Eastman Kodak Company, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us and to use your personal information appropriately.

Information for European Economic Area (EEA), Switzerland, and United Kingdom Residents
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you are located in the European Economic Area (EEA), Switzerland, or the United Kingdom, please refer to our [supplemental privacy notice](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-gdpr/) for additional information.

Information for California (CA) Residents
-----------------------------------------

If you are a resident of California, please refer to our [supplemental privacy notice](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-cpra/) for additional information required by the California Consumer Privacy Act.

Information for Brazilian Residents
-----------------------------------

If you are located in Brazil, please refer to our [supplemental privacy notice](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/information-for-brazilian-residents/) for additional information required by Federal Law No. 13,709/2018 - General Data Protection Law of Brazil ("LGPD").

Information for Cloud Services Customers
----------------------------------------

Please refer to our [Privacy Statement for Cloud Services Customers](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-statement-cloud-services/).

Privacy Notice for Professionals and Consumers
----------------------------------------------

This Privacy Notice explains how Eastman Kodak Company _(343 State Street, Rochester, NY 14650_, _USA)_ ("Kodak") uses and discloses personal information. It also applies to those Kodak affiliates, websites, applications, and other digital offerings that link to it. The goal of this Privacy Notice is to inform you of the choices you have about the way the information collected is used.

**PLEASE NOTE:** This Privacy Notice does not apply to sites hosted by unaffiliated third parties, Kodak brand licensed partners, or unaffiliated online stores that offer Kodak-branded merchandise. These companies have their own privacy policies, and questions about privacy should be directed to them.

Additionally:

* Some Kodak international sites have their own country-specific privacy notices. These will be presented to you if you use these sites.
* On our co-branded sites (such as those sites where Kodak has presented content together with one of our retail partners), a privacy notice unique to that site may be presented.
* Private sites (such as those only available to dealers and distributors) and sites created for our employees (or prospective employees) may also have privacy notices unique to those sites.

Please check the “privacy link” on the bottom of each website to read the privacy information associated with each site. You can also contact the Kodak Privacy Office at [privacy@kodak.com](mailto:privacy@kodak.com) if you have any questions.

Your Personal Information
-------------------------

Kodak's goal in collecting personal information about you is, first, to give you a meaningful, enjoyable and personalized experience and, second, to facilitate the development of new products and services relevant to customers like you. Personal information also allows us to provide better service to you by tailoring our communications to match your interests – deliver more of what you want and less of what you don't want.

At Kodak, we define “Personal Information” as any information we can use to identify, locate or contact you. It also includes other information that may be associated with your Personal Information, such as demographic data. The chart below describes the categories of personal information we collect, the sources of that information, the reasons we collect it, and the types of people to whom we may disclose the information.

Please note that we may use and disclose any personal information for our “Everyday Business Purposes”[1](#business-purposes) as permitted by law. We may disclose any personal information to our affiliates and to the service providers and contractors that need to use the information to provide services to us. We have contracts with these companies that require them to protect our information and to comply with law. We may also disclose any information at your request, such as to partners who provide co-branded pages or promotions, if we otherwise have your consent or when required by law, such as in response to a subpoena or to law enforcement agencies and courts in the United States and other countries where we operate.

We do not sell any personal information for monetary consideration. We share personal information for online targeted advertising, including cross-contextual behavioral advertising, as indicated in the chart. You can opt-out of this sharing at any time by exercising [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-choices/).  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Contact Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Your name, previous names and preferred names<br>* Business or residential mailing address<br>* Email address<br>* Work, home or mobile telephone numbers |
| **Sources** | We collect this information from you and from third party data suppliers, such as services that provide sales leads. We may also obtain your information from publicly available sources, such as LinkedIn. We may use a service provider to update or standardize mailing addresses. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use contact information to identify you and communicate with you by mail, email, telephone or text about your employment, including sending you transactional messages (such as confirmation) and commercial messages (such as marketing). Contact information is also used to personalize our communications, such as by using your preferred name. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use contact information to identify you and communicate with you by mail, email, telephone or text about your employment, including sending you transactional messages (such as confirmation) and commercial messages (such as marketing). Contact information is also used to personalize our communications, such as by using your preferred name. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose contact information to our service providers, contractors and others, such as couriers and telecommunications providers who delivery our communications. |
| **Government-issued Identification Numbers** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Social security number<br>* Tax ID number |
| **Sources** | We collect this information from you. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use this type of information for identity verification and legal compliance, such as reporting payments made to suppliers, partners or influencers as required by law. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose this information to service providers and contractors and others, such as payment processors, auditors and government agencies. |
| **Other Unique Identifiers** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Company-issued ID numbers, such as account numbers or loyalty program numbers<br>* System identifiers (e.g., usernames or online credentials)<br>* Device identifiers<br>* Advertising identifiers |
| **Sources** | We assign a unique identification number to you when you become a customer or a supplier. We collect device identifiers and other unique identifiers from your devices and from our websites, apps and platforms, which use cookies and other data collection technologies. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use unique identifiers to identify you or your device, including to associate you with different devices that you may use, for internal record-keeping and reporting, including for data matching and analytics, and to track your interactions with us, including for ad delivery and personalization. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose these identifiers to our service providers, contractors and others, such as entities that assist with our information technology programs (such as website hosting companies) or administer promotions. We may also disclose these identifiers to auditors and companies that assist with security and fraud prevention.<br><br>Advertising identifiers are shared with third parties as part of our online advertising programs. You can opt out of this sharing by exercising [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-choices/)**.** |
| **Business to Business Relationship Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | We collect “B2B” information about professionals associated with our customers, suppliers and partners in the context of our commercial relationships. This includes:<br><br>* Professional affiliations, such as your employer and information about your role<br>* Information about your authority to use our products and place orders, and about your product usage, customer service, training and related records<br>* Professional interests and credentials<br>* Information collected for supplier qualification, supplier diversity programs<br>* Preference information, including marketing and communication preferences |
| **Sources** | If you are a professional, we collect this type of information from you and from your company. We also collect B2B data from publicly available sources, such as LinkedIn, or from companies that supply leads, such as data brokers or trade shows. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use this type of information to fulfill our business relationship with you and/or our commercial partner. We also use it to develop and maintain our relationship with you, including by sending you marketing communications, personalized offers and invitations, and for internal business purposes, such as customer service, quality control, training, reporting and analytics, risk management and compliance. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We may disclose this type of information to our service providers and contractors, to the company you work for, and other companies (such as your company’s affiliates and service providers), as needed for the commercial relationship, such as including your information on purchases that you authorize or completing satisfaction surveys from your company. |
| **Consumer Relationship Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | We collect personal information about individual consumers in the context of our direct relationships with them. This includes:<br><br>* Personal characteristics, such as age, martial and family status, hobbies and interests<br>* Product and shopping preferences<br>* Communications, marketing and privacy preferences<br>* Promotions and rewards data<br>* Data from social media profiles, such as Facebook, Twitter and similar platforms |
| **Sources** | If you are a consumer, we collect this type of information from you and from other sources. For example, we may collect publicly available information about you from social media platforms. We may collect additional information from companies that provide information that helps us understand our customers, including data brokers and public records providers. We may also infer information about you based on information that you have given us and your past interactions with us and other companies. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use this type of information to better understand you and to understand our customers generally, to design products, services and programs that appeal to our customers, including loyalty programs, to identify prospective customers and for internal business purposes, such as marketing, quality control, training and analytics. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose consumer information to our service providers and contractors.  <br>As permitted by law, we may disclose consumer information to retail and marketing partners, such as companies that provide products in our Online Store, and companies with whom we have similar relationships. While we do not sell consumer information for monetary consideration, consumer information may be shared with third parties as part of our online advertising programs. You can opt out of this sharing by exercising [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-choices/). |
| **Transaction Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Customer and supplier account information, qualification data, purchase history and related records (returns, records of payments, credits _etc_.)<br>* Records related to downloads and purchases of products applications, including website and app usage and records relating to in-app purchases<br>* Customer service records<br>* Logs, such as visitor logs, server logs, and similar records |
| **Sources** | We collect this type of information from you and (if you are a professional) from your company. We receive this type of information from our service providers and contractors and from other companies, such as our payment processors, resellers or agents.<br><br>We may collect this information automatically when you visit our facilities or use our websites or apps. For example, our apps automatically log access requests, downloads and other transactions. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use this type of information to fulfill our business relationship with you and/or your company, including for customer service, recordkeeping, compliance, and dispute resolution, and to administer programs, such as promotions. We also use this information for our internal business purposes, such as finance, quality control, training, reporting and analytics, and for risk management, fraud prevention and similar purposes. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose transaction information to our service providers, contractors and others, such as to other entities as needed to complete the transaction, including delivery companies, agents and manufacturers, and to our auditors, financial institutions, and government agencies. If you are a professional, we may disclose this information to your company. |
| **Financial information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Bank account number and details<br>* Payment card information |
| **Sources** | We collect this type of information from you and from our service providers, financial institutions and payment processors. For transactions in our online stores, payment card information is collected by our payment processors and not stored by Kodak. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use financial information to fulfill our business relationship with you, such as processing payments, issuing refunds and collections, and for internal business purposes, such as finance functions, audits, fraud prevention and compliance. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose financial information to our service providers, contractors and others, such as payment processors, financial institutions, auditors and government agencies. |
| **Health Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Information needed to accommodate disabilities<br>* Information about workplace accidents and occupational safety |
| **Sources** | We may collect health information from you if you need assistance accessing our products, services or facilities. We may collect this heath information from you and from others, such as in connection with a workplace accident. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use health data to accommodate disabilities and enable accessibility of our products, services and facilities, and for occupational health and safety programs and other internal business purposes, such as risk management and compliance. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose health information to our service providers, contractors and others, such as healthcare providers, insurers, first responders (in the event of an emergency), or government agencies. We may also disclose health information to others if needed to provide you with an accommodation. |
| **Online & Technical Information**<br><br>**_Please read our statement about_** _**[Cookies & Online Privacy](#cookies-online-privacy)**_ **_for additional information._** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * IP address<br>* Device identifiers and other information about devices that connect to our networks<br>* Precise geolocation data from your device<br>* System and server logs, including access logs<br>* Data from cookies, pixel tags or other online tools |
| **Sources** | We collect this type of information from your computer or devices when you interact with our platforms, websites and applications. For example, when you visit our websites, our server logs record your IP address and other information. We may also receive this information from others, such as security services and advertising partners. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use technical information for system administration, technology management, including optimizing our websites and applications, and for information security and cybersecurity purposes, including detecting threats to our networks and systems.<br><br>We use precise geolocation data to provide location-based services. We may also use this information for information security and fraud prevents, and for internal business purposes, such as analytics.<br><br>We also use online and technical information for personalization, to better understand our customers and prospective customers and to enhance our relationship information, including by associating you with different devices and browsers, and for online targeting and advertising purposes. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We may disclose this type of information to our service providers and contractors, and others such as companies that support our information technology and cybersecurity programs. We do not share precise geolocation data, but other Online and Technical Information may be shared with third parties as part of our online advertising programs. You can opt out of this sharing by exercising [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-choices/)**.** |
| **Audio Visual Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Photograph<br>* Video images, videoconference records<br>* CCTV recordings<br>* Call center recordings and call monitoring records<br>* Voicemails |
| **Sources** | We collect this type of information from you and from publicly available sources, such as social media sites. We may also collect this information automatically, such as when we record calls to our call center and use CCTV cameras in our facilities. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use this type of information for internal business purposes, such as call recordings used for training, quality control, and compliance. We also use these data for relationship purposes, such as use of photos and videos for social media purposes or sentiment analytics, and for security purposes and loss prevention. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We may disclose this type of information to our service providers and contractors that support our information technology, security, and loss prevention programs. |
| **Inferred and Derived Information** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Propensities, attributes and/or scores generated by internal analytics programs and used for marketing<br>* Propensities, attributes and/or scores generated by internal analytics programs and used for information security and fraud purposes |
| **Sources** | We create inferred and derived data elements by analyzing other data, such as our relationship information, transactional information and online and technical information. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We combine inferred data with other relationship information and use this type of information to better understand you and to understand our customers generally, to design products, services and programs that appeal to our customers, including loyalty programs, to identify prospective customers and for internal business purposes, such as quality control, training and analytics. We use inferred data to improve our security and fraud detection models. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose derived information to our service providers, contractors and others, such as management consulting firms and security firms. |
| **Children’s Data** |     |
| We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose any personal information of children under 16. |     |
| **Compliance Data** |     |
| **Representative Data Elements** | * Compliance program data, including customer screening records, and other record maintained to demonstrate compliance with applicable laws, such as tax laws, product safety laws, licensing laws, _etc._<br>* Occupational and environmental safety records<br>* Intellectual property protection program records<br>* Records relating to complaints and internal investigations<br>* Records related to the exercise of privacy rights<br>* Records related to security incidents, including any security breach notifications<br>* Records maintained by the company legal department |
| **Sources** | We collect compliance data from you and from our providers, contractors, and others, such as screening companies service, investigators, legal advisors and government agencies. For example, Kodak employs technology and uses public watch list data obtained from [Descartes Systems Group](https://www.descartes.com/resources/knowledge-center/descartes-denied-party-screeningtm-descartes-dpstm) to screen all export orders in compliance with U.S. Federal and International rules and regulations regarding export controls for denied and restricted parties. We may generate compliance records internally, such as when we document a workplace event. |
| **Primary Purposes for Collecting** | We use compliance data for internal governance, corporate ethics programs, institutional risk management, reporting, demonstrating compliance and accountability externally, and as needed for litigation and defense of claims. |
| **Categories of Recipients** | We disclose compliance to our service providers, contractors and others, such as auditors, investigators, lawyers, advisors, government agencies and others as required by law. |

Cookies and Online Privacy
--------------------------

When you visit our website, use our mobile applications, or engage with our online ads or email communications, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, browser analysis tools, server logs and web beacons.

In many cases, the information we collect using these tools is only used in a non-identifiable way, without any reference to Personal Information. For example, we use information we collect about all website users to optimize our websites and to understand website traffic patterns. In some cases, we do associate the information we collect using cookies and other technology with your Personal Information. Our Privacy Notice describes how we use that information when we associate it with your Personal Information. This Cookies and Online Privacy section provides more information about our collection and use of Online and Technical Information.

**_We collect personal information and non-personal information using cookies._** A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a website visitor’s computer or device to uniquely identify the visitor’s web browser and to store information or settings in the browser. You can control cookies by changing your browser’s setting.

Our websites use four kinds of cookies:

* _Strictly necessary cookies_, which are required for our website to operate properly. For example, strictly necessary cookies allow you to set your privacy preferences, log in or fill in forms. Some strictly necessary cookies are used to help ensure the security of our websites.
* _Performance cookies_, which allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.
* _Functional cookies,_ which enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalization. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages.
* _Targeting cookies_, which may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information information, but are based on uniquely identifying your brower and internet device.

When you visit our websites, we will always place strictly necessary cookies. You have choices about performance, functional and targeting cookies. You can use our Cookie Management Platform to control which of these cookies you wish to accept or to reject all non-necessary cookies. If you exercise your rights to tell us not to sell/share your information or to not to use your information for online targeted advertising, we will refrain from placing third party performance cookies and advertising cookies on your browser.

**_Our websites use Pixel Tags._** Pixel tags, also known as tracking pixels, web beacons or clear GIFs, are tools used to transmit information to our service providers’ or partner’s servers. When you visit a website or open an email that contains a web beacon, that tool will instruct your browser to transmit information such as your IP address, device details, time of the activity, and nature of the activity (_e.g.,_ email read, web pages visited) to us. These tools allow us to measure response to our communications and to improve our websites. They also enable partners to compile information about your browsing activity on the websites for personalization and online targeted advertising. If you exercise your rights to tell us not to share your information or not to use your information for online targeted advertising, we will refrain from placing pixel tags on your browser.

**_Our websites collect personal information using Server Logs._** A server log is a text file that records activities on our web services. When you visit a website, we log the date and time of your visit, the device you use to access our website, your operating system type, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. Our server logs also record the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. An IP address is a unique identifier that devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. We may also collect information about the website you were visiting before you came to Kodak and the website you visit after you leave our site. We use this information in aggregate, such as to analyze website traffic patterns and to better understand website user behavior generally. We also use the information for security purposes, to detect threats, and for fraud prevention. For example, we may block login attempts coming from countries where we do not do business. We do not sell or share the information collected by our logs, and we do not use this information for online targeted advertising.

**_Our websites use third party analytics services, such as Google Analytics._** Analytics services help us understand how people use our websites. In some cases, these services are provided by companies that act as service providers for us, meaning that they do not use the information collected for their own purposes. In other cases, the company may combine information collected from users of our websites with information collected from other websites. You have the right to opt-out of having your data combined by these third parties. You can use our Cookie Management Platform to reject all non-necessary cookies. If you exercise your rights to tell us not to sell/share your information or to not to use your information for online targeted advertising, we will also refrain from placing third party cookies on your browser.

Additional information about the third party analytics companies that collect data on our websites:

* To learn more and opt out of data collection through Google Analytics: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en)
* To learn more and opt out of data collection through Microsoft Clarity: [https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/clarity/faq](https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/clarity/faq) and [https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

**_Our websites integrate with Social Media Platforms._** Our websites may enable you to interact with us and others via social media platforms, such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, LinkedIn and Instagram. We may also allow you to login to our websites using social media platform credentials. While we respect each social media platform’s privacy policies, we may collect personal information about you and your friends if you choose to use these tools. If you engage with our content on or through a social media site, you may allow us to have access to certain information associated with your social media account (e.g., name, username, email address, profile picture).

Additionally, social media platforms collect persistent identifiers through your browser or mobile operating system, so they may collect information about your use of our websites. If you have previously provided personally identifiable information to these platforms, the platform operators may recognize you here. Your use of social network plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy. For more information, please read the privacy policies posted by the social media platforms that you use.

We may also display interest-based ads to you when you are using social media platforms. These platforms allow us to personalize the ads that we display to you. We may convert your email address into a unique number which can be matched by the platform with its user to allow delivery of the advertising. You can opt-out of online targeted advertising by exercising [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.kodak.com/en/company/page/privacy-choices/)**.**

**_We collect information when you use our Mobile Applications._** We offer mobile applications that in some cases allow you to access your account, interact with us online and receive other information via your smartphone. Personal Information collected by Kodak via our mobile applications that link to our Privacy Notice are handled in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Notice.

When you use our website or download our mobile apps, you may choose to allow us to obtain your precise location. We use this information to customize our response to your requests. For example, If you are searching for a Kodak product or service, we will display the ones in your area; we may share your location with third party mapping services (e.g., Apple Maps, Google Maps) to accomplish this. We may also offer automatic (or "push") notifications. We will provide push notifications only to those customers who opt-in to receive such notifications from us. You do not have to provide location information to us or enable push notifications to use any of our mobile apps. If you have questions about location and notification privacy, please contact your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.

Your Privacy Rights
-------------------

Kodak offers you different choices about how we communicate with you and use your information.

* You can limit the information you provide to Kodak. Participation in promotions and programs is voluntary.
* You can limit the communications Kodak sends to you. To opt-out of marketing emails, simply click the link labeled “unsubscribe” at the bottom of any marketing email we send you. For additional information about declining e-mail from Kodak, visit [www.kodak.com/go/unsubscribe](http://www.kodak.com/go/unsubscribe). _Please note that even if you opt-out of marketing emails, we may still need to contact you with important transactional information about your account. For example, even if you opt-out, we may still send you activity confirmations or fraud alerts._
* To revoke permissions you may have given to send text messages, text STOP in response to any message.

If you are a registered user, you can review and update your profile using your username and password. You can also contact your Customer Service Representative.

In addition to these choices, we respect the rights you may have under any applicable privacy laws. Depending on your country or state or residence, these rights may include:

* The right to be informed about our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information,
* The right to know if we maintain your personal information, and if we do, to access that information (subject to the rights of others) and to request that we provide your information in a portable format,
* The right to ask us to correct your information if it is incomplete or incorrect,
* The right to ask that we delete your personal information, and
* The right to object to our processing of your personal information, including the rights to object to:
    * the sale of your personal information,
    * the sharing or use of your personal information for certain types of online targeted advertising,
    * the use of profiling or automated decision-making which might significantly affect you,
    * certain secondary uses and disclosures of sensitive personal information, and,
    * if we are processing your personal information based on your consent, to withdraw your consent at any time.

To learn more about the specific rights that you have and to exercise your rights, please visit our privacy rights portal at Your Privacy Choices. You can also contact us at [privacy@kodak.com](mailto:privacy@kodak.com).

Please understand that these rights are subject to some limitations. For example, we may require documentation to support certain corrections to your information, and we generally cannot restrict or delete personal information in those situations where our retention is required for our internal business purposes or to comply with law.

We will not retaliate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

Protecting Your Information
---------------------------

Kodak implements a variety of administrative, managerial and technical security measures to help protect your personal information in line with applicable laws and regulations. Kodak has Internal Control Standards which relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls, such as encryption, to help safeguard the information we collect online. For example, we use technology like encryption to protect sensitive Personal Information (such as your account number) during transmission. We will retain your Personal Information for as long as the information is needed for the purposes listed above and for any additional period that may be required or permitted by law

Social Security Number Protection Policy
----------------------------------------

In the U.S., Kodak collects Social Security numbers in the ordinary course of its business. Kodak has implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative safeguards to help protect the Social Security numbers from unlawful use and unauthorized disclosure. All associates and contractors are required to follow these established procedures, both online and offline. Access to Social Security numbers is limited to those employees and contractors who have a need to access the information to perform tasks for Kodak. Social Security numbers are only disclosed to those service providers, auditors, advisors, and/or successors-in-interest who are legally or contractually obligated to protect them or as required or permitted by law.

International Transfers
-----------------------

Kodak is based in the U.S. and operates globally, with affiliates and service providers located around the world. As a result, your Personal Information may be transferred to, stored at or processed in other countries, including the U.S., which may not have equivalent privacy or data protection laws. However, regardless of where your Personal Information is transferred, we will protect it in accordance with this Privacy Notice and applicable law.

Where required, we use approved Standard Contractual Clauses and other approved data transfer mechanisms to assure that personal data is adequately protected. Please contact [privacy@kodak.com](mailto:privacy@kodak.com) if you would like more information about cross-border transfers or to obtain a copy of any applicable Standard Contractual Clauses.

Communities
-----------

Some of our sites may enable you to participate in public services such as discussion boards, chats, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal data about yourself when using these services. Be aware when you disclose personal data at these sites, such as your name, member name, e-mail address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited e-mail. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected.

Outside Links
-------------

Our websites contain links to other websites for your convenience and information. Some Kodak websites contain links to and functionality that integrates with platforms like LinkedIn, Facebook and Twitter. We may also provide links that allow you to access and interact with other retail partners and other companies that are not affiliated with Kodak, such as our partners. When you intentionally interact with another company though these links, that company’s own policy will govern the personal information that you provide. Kodak is not responsible for the privacy practices of these platforms or websites. Kodak encourages you to ascertain the privacy practices of those websites.

Job Applicants
--------------

If you have applied for employment with Kodak, the Personal Information submitted with your job application will be used only for recruitment and other customary human resources purposes including any required government reporting and recordkeeping obligations. Please see our [Privacy Notice for Job Applicants (Word doc)](https://trmx.brassring.com/JetStream/500/Presentation/Template/ASP/Candidate/Todo/CandidateProfileDwnld.asp?filename=%4095IL4i2Ju2cLcIPUUcEdyyOb85T5R1L1zvI%2FBWCUg1qVfU%2BO5zKVyoTe5FldGDHRZpw6FQ6kjmBGLBBR0mgvyl5E3gNM3pH1FoejPizntJKP7eI1XakwqXUW1lnGaBimt5IvrOPpsQgofvfaKn2HNLHAQvacg5Mq72G2fH1bNKjGu9ve9MAFAict2aKPnRzk8tB09bAgix57LyGvvC03%2F6jcnTrxbONsnBYzZMb3Z0ziHThp5ErbfhW%2BkS1%2Bj8%2B%2FJ7RY0PKHXebT5CkUFfzAONWpUQLC9R%2FXqxtcebwcGkM%3D&EmailTemplate=true).

How to Reach Us
---------------

If you have questions or concerns about your privacy, please contact us by e-mail at [privacy@kodak.com](mailto:privacy@kodak.com) or by mail to:

Eastman Kodak Company  
Privacy Office  
13th Floor, Bldg. 7  
343 State Street  
Rochester, NY 14650-0205

Kodak's Privacy Office will work with you to resolve any concerns you have.

Changes to this Privacy Notice
------------------------------

Kodak reserves the right to update this Privacy Notice from time to time. In the event of a material change, we will post a prominent announcement on this page, and in the event of a material change that affects previously-collected personal information, we will notify customers whose personal information will be impacted by email.

* * *

\[1\] **Everyday Business Purposes** encompasses the Business Purposes (as defined by California law) and following related purposes for which any personal information may processed:

* To provide the information, product or service requested by the individual or as reasonably expected given the context in which with the personal information was collected (such as customer credentialing, providing customer service and preference management, providing product updates, bug fixes or recalls, and dispute resolution)
* For identity and credential management, including identity verification and authentication, system and technology administration
* To protect the security and integrity of systems, networks, applications and data, including detecting, analyzing and resolving security threats, and collaborating with cybersecurity centers, consortia and law enforcement about imminent threats
* For fraud detection and prevention,
* For legal and regulatory compliance, including all uses and disclosures of personal information that are required by law or for reasonably needed for compliance with company policies and procedures, such as: anti-money laundering programs, security and incident response programs, intellectual property protection and anti-piracy programs, and corporate ethics and compliance hotlines,
* For corporate audit, analysis and reporting,
* To enforce our contracts and to protect against injury, theft, legal liability, fraud or abuse, to protect people or property, including physical security programs
* To de-identify the data or create aggregated datasets, such as for consolidating reporting, research or analytics,
* To make back-up copies for business continuity and disaster recovery purposes, and
* For corporate governance, including mergers, acquisitions and divestitures.

Print

Arrow Down

Advanced Materials & Chemicals

Arrow Down

Motion Picture

Arrow Down

Consumer

Arrow Down

Company

Arrow Down

Globe

English ▼

* Cookie Preferences

Copyright ©2024 Eastman Kodak Company. All Rights Reserved.
